S.M. Hasan



S.M. Mahamudul Hasan 10/08/1998 1

PROFILE

Professional WordPress developer with more than two years of experience. Highly motivated, energetic and adaptable individual seeking to obtain a part time or contract based web development position where i can apply my designing and development skills.

WORK EXPERIENCE

WordPress Developer 06/2018 – present Fiverr, sylhet , bangladesh

- WordPress Solution
- · Custom website design

eCommerce website 05/2020 – present **developer**

Upwork, Jessore, Bangladesh

- eCommerce UI/UX design
- eCommerce website development
- Multi-vendor/Affiliate eCommerce creation.

Freelance Web Developer 03/2020 – 03/2020 Atgrowthspace, Edmonton, Alberta., Canada

- · Full Stack development
- UI/UX design

EDUCATION

Bachelor's degree 01/2017 - present Shahjalal University of Science and Technology, Sylhet, Bangladesh

Four year Bachelor degree in Computer Science and Engineering.

High School and College 01/2010 - 04/2016 Akij Collegiate School, Jessore, Bangladesh

Professional Web design 02/2019 – present udemy

★ SKILLS

WordPress Website development

Web UI/UX design

eCommerce website development

LANGUAGES







Bengali

English

Hindi

AWARDS

INNOVATIVE IDEAS
DESIGN AWARDS

01/2020

CREATIVE UX/UI DESIGN AWARDS

06/2020

04/2020

PROJECTS

Growth-space || Accounting and Tax Website

https://atgrowthspace.com/

- Full Stack development
- PHP, MySQL, JavaScript, bootstrap, HTML, CSS.
- UI/UX design

helloorganica || Bio Beauty E commerce Website

02/2020

https://helloorganica.com/

- eCommerce website
- PHP, MySQL, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap.
- WordPress Woo-commerce plugin

Bangla Fake News

04/2020

http://hasanstudio.xyz/Fake_news/

- · News portal development
- · HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP
- WordPress blog.

NY-Bagel || Restaurant eCommerce Website

06/2019

https://nybagelrancho.online/

- · Small eCommerce website
- PHP, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, MySQL, Bootstrap.
- WordPress woo-commerce plugin